One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
They Believe in Me
قد آمنوا بي
I understand your frustration.
أدرك أنّ هذا مزعج
You tried to get up, and I didn't let you.
حاولت النهوض، فعرقلت قدمك
You tried to throw a left punch, so I hit your left shoulder.
حاولت أن تلكمني بيدك اليسرى، فضربت كتفك الأيسر
You tried to throw a right punch, so I hit your right shoulder.
حاولت أن تلكمني بيدك اليمنى، فضربت كتفك الأيمن
All of this shows that you're just an idiot who can do nothing but feel frustrated.
كل ذلك يدل على أنّك مجرد أحمق عاجز يشعر بالإنزعاج
That's how it is when your every move is easily predicted.
وهذا ما يحدث حين يتنبّأ خصمك بجميع تحركاتك
But... I don't want to just make you feel frustrated...
...لكن جعلك تشعر بالإنزعاج ليس كافيًا
Whether it's a left kick or a right kick...
...ركلة يسرى أو ركلة يمنى
I'll hit you before you can do anything.
سأضربك قبل أن تفعل أي شيء
And I'll keep it up until your heart bursts in half.
وسأستمر في ذلك حتّى تلقى حتفك
Every attack has an intent...
لكل هجوم إرادة
and a presence!
وهيئة
Don't just attack blindly, Luffy!
لا تهاجم بشكل عشوائي يا لوفي
Take this!
خذ هذه
As I thought...
...إنّه بالفعل
he's beginning to see the future in the same way I do.
بدأ في رؤية المستقبل كما أفعل
Oh, shoot!
اللعنة
Bege's Ship, At Sea
سفينة بيجي في البحر
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
I forgot to pipe roses of whipped cream
نسيتُ إضافة الورود على الكريمة المخفوقة في أعلى الكعكة
I'll do it!
سأتولى الأمر
Give me a pastry bag!
أعطوني كيس تزيين الحلويات
Yes, sir!
حاضر
Sky Walk!
خطوات السماء
Amazing!
مذهل
So beautiful!
أحسنت
All right! It's finished!
عظيم، اكتملت
Yes!
أجل
Finally!
أخيرًا
The ultimate wedding cake—one that will stop Big Mom—is finished!
لإيقاف هيجان بيغ مام، انتهينا من إعداد أعظم كعكة زفاف
It smells so good... It's making me feel faint-rero.
يا لها من رائحة زكية، سيغمى عليّ-ريرو
I don't know what else to say!
أنا لا أعرف ماذا أقول
We didn't even need to add any poison!
لا داعي لتسميمها
I hope Big Mom will drop dead from deliciousness!
فبيغ مام سترسل للسماء من شدّة لذّتها
Great! We made it in time!
هذا مطمئن، انتهينا في الوقت المناسب
Madam Pudding!
بودينغ-ساما
Hey, are you guys okay?!
هل أنتم بخير يا رفاق؟
The cooks are collapsing one after another!
الطُهاة ينهارون واحدًا تلو الآخر
They must have worked too hard!
يا لها من عملية طهو مروعة
Don't stand up again. We know your plan.
لا تنهض مجدّدًا، فنحن على درايةٍ بما تخططون له
"Cacao Island at one a.m.".
«جزيرة الكاكاو في الساعة الواحدة صباحًا»
But of course, your friends will be wiped out before they even get close to Cacao Island.
وبالطبع، سيُقضى عليكم قبل أن تصلوا إلى جزيرة الكاكاو
They will be greeted by my younger brothers' fleets.
إخوتي وأساطيلهم ينتظرونكم هناك
It'll be the same for you, even if you do manage to get out of here.
لذا ستلقى المصير ذاته حتّى لو خرجت من هنا
But...
...مع ذلك
I'll definitely... make it through the mirror!
سأخرج من إحدى المرايا بلا شك
Why are you talking like you'll succeed?
لماذا تتحدث وكأنّك ستنجح؟
Pudding-chan ! Chiffon-chan !
بودينغ-تشان، شيفون-تشان
I couldn't have done it without your help. Thanks!
لم يكن هذا ليتحقق دون مساعدتكما، شكرًا لكما
With this cake...
...بهذه الكعكة
I can save my friends for sure!
سنتمكن من إنقاذ رفاقي بلا شك
What makes you so certain?! Sure, the cake is done,
هل أنت متأكد من ذلك؟ صحيح أننا انتهينا من إعداد الكعكة
but your friends could be dead already!
لكن ربما رفاقك قد ماتوا أصلًا
Even if they're alive, you don't know whether Mama will like the cake or not!
وحتّى لو كانوا على قيد الحياة فلا يمكنك أن تضمن بأنّ الكعكة ستنال على إعجاب ماما
It's a waste of time to transport this crappy cake, Sanji...
...لا فائدة من نقل هذه الكعكة الرديئة يا سانجي
...-san !
سان-
That's not what you meant to say, Pudding!
أنتِ مخطئة يا بودينغ
Oh! No, I didn't mean it! What am I saying?!
أخطأت، أخطأت، ما الذي أتفوه به؟
In any case, I've got to get going...
مهما كان الأمر، يجب أن أذهب
Wait!
انتظروا
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
Rumble! Monster Point!
كرة رمبل: هيئة الوحش
I will stop her!
سأردعها
What the hell is that?! Are there only monsters on that ship?!
ما ذلك بحق؟ ألا يوجد إلّا الوحوش على متن تلك السفينة؟
Napoleon! Extend yourself!
نابليون، تمدد أكثر
Yes, Mama!
حاضر يا ماما
Chopper, Brook, Jinbe! If we can hold out here, then...
تشوبر، بروك، جينبي، إن ...استطعنا الصمود هنا، فعندها
Yeah, I know!
أجل، أدرك ذلك
You don't need to say it.
لا حاجة لتذكيرنا
Mm-hm!
أجل
Until that moment comes, endure it no matter what!
يجب أن نصمد مهما حدث إلى أن تحين تلك اللحظة
I'll bring the best cake ever to stop Big Mom...
سأحضر أفضل كعكة على الإطلاق لإيقاف بيغ مام
I'm gonna kick your ass...
سوف أُبرحك ضربًا
and make it through the mirror.
وسأخرج حتمًا من إحدى المرايا
Because they...
...لأنّهم
...believe in me!
يثقون بي
I'll cut you in half!
سأقطعك إلى نصفين
Cloven Palm!
كف الحافر
Chopper!
تشوبر
Gust Sword!
عاصفة السيف
Soul Parade!
موكب الروح
Cognac!
نصل الإمبراطور
Stop!
توقفي
Chopper! You can't fight anymore!
تشوبر، هذا مستحيل
I've got no choice! Come on, Big Mom!
حتّى لو كان الأمر مستحيلًا، أريني ما لديكِ يا بيغ مام
At the very least, I can drag you down with me into the sea!
يمكنني على الأقل سحبكِ معي للغرق في البحر
You're full of spirit.
روحك المعنوية مرتفعة
Then, do you think you'll be able to take me on after this?
إذًا، هل يمكنك أن تسحبني معك هكذا؟
No... way...
...هذا... محال
At that size, even seawater won't help us!
بهذه الضخامة، حتّى مياه البحر لن تنفع ضده
So... that's the soul of an emperor!
هذه روح الإمبراطورة إذًا
Now, try to get away as far as you can!
والآن، لنرَ لأي مدى يمكنكم الهرب
If nothing is done, we'll get burned up along with the Sunny !
إن لم نتصرف، فسنتحرق مع السفينة
Even though we made it this far!
بعدما وصلنا إلى هذا الحد
And Sanji-kun should be here any moment now!
وكاد يحين وصول سانجي-كن
You all showed me a good time...
كانت مطاردتكم ممتعة
Now, give me the cake...
والآن، أعطوني الكعكة
What is this...
...ما هذه
delicious smell?
الرائحة الزكية؟
Don't stand up again! You stand no chance!
لا تنهض مجدّدًا، فأنت لا تمتلك فرصة
This fool's observation haki is getting as good as mine!
إنّه يقترب شيئًا فشيئًا من مستوى هاكي الملاحظة لدي
I have to get rid of him soon, or something unexpected could happen!
إن لم أجهز عليه حالًا، فقد يحدث ما لم يكن بالحسبان
Mochi...
دفعة
Thrust!
الموتشي
That ship...
...تلك السفينة
Guys!
يا رفاق
A ship is here!
وصلت السفينة
It's got the cake onboard!
وعلى متنها الكعكة
Sanji-kun and the others baked the cake and came back for us!
سانجي-كن والآخرين أعدّوا الكعكة وجلبوها معهم
Oh, Sanji!
سانجي
Sanji-san !
سانجي-سان
Mama!
ماما
It smells so sweet!
يا لها من رائحة زكية
There it is, Black Leg. It's your ship!
تلك سفينتكم أيها الساق السوداء
That damn Prometheus. He's gotten huge because of Big Mom's soul!
بروميثيوس اللعين أصبح ضخمًا بسبب روح بيغ مام
And riding on top of the giant Prometheus, I see Big Mom-rero.
كما أنني أرى بيغ مام تمتطي بروميثيوس الضخم-ريرو
Father! Beyond them, it's...
...فاذر، خلفهم يوجد
Perospero and...
...بيروسبيرو وأيضًا
Bavarois...
...بافروا
along with Smoothie and the others!
بالإضافة إلى سموذي والآخرين
They're being chased by quite a troublesome fleet!
يا له من أسطولٍ مزعج يطاردهم
Their ship's taken heavy damage, too!
كما أنّ سفينتهم تعرّضت لأضرار بالغة
Man your positions, men!
استعدوا يا رجال
Yeah!
أجل
We're up against Big Mom! Keep your guards up!
نحن بصدد مواجهة بيغ مام، لا ترخوا دفاعكم
But if you see an opening, fill her with bullets!
لكن إن سنحت لكم الفرصة، فامطروها بالرصاص
– Yeah! – Rero !
أجل
Nami-san ! I'm here to save you!
نامي-سوان، أتيت لإنقاذك
Anyway, Big Mom and Perospero have to have been chasing them for hours...
لكن، مطاردة بيغ مام وبيروسبيرو ...لهم طوال الساعات الماضية
I'm impressed that they survived! Especially without a captain to lead them!
وتمكنهم من النجاة رغم غياب قائدهم لهو أمر مثير للإعجاب بحق
Nami-swan !
نامي-سوان
There's someone on the bow! Do you feel that weird aura?!
ثمة شخص يقف على مقدمة السفينة لكن، ما هذه الطاقة الغريبة حوله؟
Well, it isn't haki... Why are they on Bege's ship?
أيًّا كانت، فهي ليست هاكي لكن لماذا أتوا على متن سفينة بيجي؟
Hm? Someone's dancing on the bow of that ship!
ماذا؟ ثمة شخص يرقص على مقدمة السفينة
Who cares about that?! The cake is what matters!
دعك منه، الأهم هي الكعكة
Lick!
بيرورين
They definitely recreated the cake that we saw at the wedding!
أعدّوا كعكة زفاف مثل التي رأيناها في الحفل بالفعل
If Mama likes how it tastes, her ravenous rampage will end! But...
إن نال مذاقها على إعجاب ماما ...فستتوقف نوبة جوعها، لكن
Bege is there! That cake has to be poisoned!
بما أنّ بيجي موجود هناك، أكاد أجزم أنّ الكعكة مسمومة
What should I do?!
ما العمل؟ ما العمل؟ ما العمل؟ ما العمل؟
Thanks to that sweet smell, she's stopped attacking us...
لم تكمل هجومها بفضل الرائحة الزكية
I thought...
...ظننت
we were going to die...
بأنني هالك لا محالة
Should we destroy that cake?!
هل يجدر بنا تدمير الكعكة؟
No, if we do that, there will be no stopping Mama's ravenous rampage,
كلا، إن فعلنا ذلك فلن يكون بحوزتنا شيء لإيقاف نوبة جوع ماما، وستدمّر الدولة بأكملها
Oh... but, if she eats the poisoned cake and dies...
ومن جهة أخرى، إن ماتت ماما مسمومة من الكعكة فسينتهي أمر الدولة وطاقم قراصنتها
What should I do?! Which option should I choose?!
ما العمل؟ أي الاحتمالان أختار؟
Hey, Black Leg!
أيها الساق السوداء
We held up our end of the deal! Now we'll take the cake.
ستكون هذه الكعكة بحوزتنا كما اتفقنا
As promised, we won't do a thing until Mama eats it and is full.
وكما وعدناك، لن نفعل شيئًا حتّى تأكل ماما وتشبع
But...
...لكن
after that, we're free to do whatever we want, got it?!
أنا حُر في فعل أي شيء بعد ذلك، صحيح؟
Do whatever you want. Our mission was to pacify Big Mom with this cake.
افعل ما شئت، فمهمتنا تتمثّل في تهدئة بيغ مام بواسطة الكعكة
We can stop her!
يمكننا إيقافها
We're ready, Sanji...
...نحن على أهبة الاستعداد يا سانجي
...-san !
سان-
I'm coming!
أنا قادم
You'd better hurry up if you don't want to die!
أسرع أيها الوغد إن لم تكن تريد الموت
Pudding!
بودينغ
Take care of yourself!
اعتنِ بنفسك
Are you happy now?
هل أنتِ سعيدة الآن؟
Yes, very...
للغاية
Goodbye, Sister...
إلى اللقاء يا أختي
Rabiyan! Super Express!
رابيان، انطلق بأقصى سرعة
Go fast enough so that Big Brother Peros and Big Brother Bavarois don't notice us!
انطلق بسرعة من أجل ألّا يرانا أخواي بيروس وبافروا
Okay!
أجل
My wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف خاصتي
There it is!
ها هي
I finally found it! Let's go!
عثرتُ عليها أخيرًا، لنذهب
Yes!
حاضر
Mama!
ماما
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
Here she comes! To starboard!
إنّها قادمة، اتجهوا نحو اليمين
Yes, sir!
حاضر
Full speed southwest! Head toward Liqueur Island!
أديروا الدفة نحو الجنوب الغربي، سنذهب إلى جزيرة الخمر
Lick?
بيرورين؟
Minister Perospero! The ship with the cake has changed course!
بيروسبيرو-ساما، السفينة التي تنقل الكعكة غيّرت مسارها
Why?!
لماذا؟
Mama is being lured by the cake and has started chasing Bege's ship!
لقد استدرجوا ماما بالكعكة، فهي تلحق بسفينة بيجي حاليًّا
Straw Hat's ship and Bege's ship...
...سفينة قبعة القش وسفينة بيجي
By splitting up, they're trying to divide us...
إنّهم يحاولون تقسيمنا بانفصالهم
Lick!
بيرورين
Yo! I'm back!
أهلًا، لقد عدت
Sanji-kun !
سانجي-كن
Sanji-san ! Pudding-san !
سانجي-سان، بودينغ-سان
Sanji!
سانجي
We were barely hanging on! I thought we were done for! Thank you!
كنا على وشك أن نموت، شكرًا لك
I'm glad that you're okay!
يسعدني أنّك بخير
I love you, too! Nami-swan !
أنا أحبك أيضًا يا نامي-سوان
By the way, Sanji-san, why were you on Bege's ship?
بالمناسبة يا سانجي-سان، لماذا كنت على متن سفينة بيجي؟
It's a long story...
إنّها قصة طويلة
Where is Bege's ship heading?
إلى أين تتجه سفينة بيجي؟
We don't know what Mom will do after she eats the cake...
لا نضمن ما ستفعله بيغ مام بعد تناولها للكعكة
so they're taking the cake to the nearest island.
لهذا السبب سيأخذون الكعكة لأقرب جزيرة
What? So they decided to be bait?!
ماذا؟ سيؤدون دور الطُعم إذًا؟
Why are they doing that?!
لِمَ عساهم يفعلون ذلك؟
They haven't given up on killing her.
يبدو أنّه ما زال يريد اغتيالها
I see. That sounds just like Bege.
فهمت، هذه طبيعة بيجي
This ship's safety is the only thing that matters to me.
طالما هذه السفينة بأمان، فلا مانع لدي
It'll be great if they can lure Mom away.
إن استدرج بيغ مام بعيدًا عنّا، فسيصب ذلك في صالحنا
In any case...
...لكن
Our ship has taken a lot of damage...
تعرّضت السفينة لأضرار بالغة
I'm sorry. I should've done better...
...المعذرة، أخفقت في حمايتها
What are you talking about, Jinbe?! If it weren't for you, we probably would have...
...عمّ تتحدث؟ لولا وجودك يا جينبي لكنّا على الأرجح
Let's talk about it later. I'm really glad that you're okay.
لنؤجل الحديث، أنا حقًّا سعيد أنّكم بخير
By the way, where are Pedro and Carrot-chan ?
بالمناسبة، أين بيدرو وكاروت-تشان؟
Um...
...ذلك
Oh, th-they're sleeping inside! They both got exhausted from fighting...
إنّهما نائمان بالداخل، فكلاهما مرهقان بسبب القتال
Brother Peros, what should we do?!
أخي بيروس، ما العمل؟
Straw Hat's ship or Mama, which one should we chase?!
أنلحق بسفينة قبعة القش أم ماما؟
This is... Bege...
معك بيجي
Bege! You bastard! What are you up to?!
يا بيجي الوغد، ما الذي تخطط له؟
And why is the cake on your ship?!
لِمَ الكعكة على متن سفينتك؟
We'll deal with Mama's ravenous rampage.
سنتولى أمر نوبة جوع ماما
We'll let her eat the cake and then make sure she's comfortable.
سنجعلها تأكل الكعكة حتّى تشبع وتهدأ
Don't lie, you traitor! What did you put in the cake?!
لا تكذب أيها الخائن ماذا وضعت في الكعكة؟
We didn't put anything in it. You know Pudding made the cake, right?
لم أضع شيئًا، ألا تعلم أنّ بودينغ من أعدّت الكعكة؟
Oh, yeah! Where's Pudding?!
صحيح أيها الوغد، أين بودينغ؟
You don't need to worry about Mama or Pudding right now.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ماما أو بودينغ إطلاقًا
Just relax and focus on the Straw Hats.
اطمئن وركز على مطاردة قبعة القش
You son of a–
أيها اللعين
Hey, Bege!
مهلًا يا بيجي
Let's chase Bege, Bavarois!
لنطارد بيجي يا بافروا
What?!
ماذا؟
Look at them! I'm one hundred percent sure that they're scheming to kill Mama.
انظر إليهم، أنا على يقين تام بأنّهم يخططون لقتل ماما
And Pudding might be dead!
وربما قتلوا بودينغ بالفعل
But Brother Peros! What about the Straw Hats' ship?!
لكن يا أخي بيروس، ما العمل بشأن سفينة قبعة القش؟
They'll sink at Cacao Island anyway! Also...
...ستغرق عند جزيرة الكاكاو على أي حال، وأيضًا
Who do you think is also chasing the Straw Hats' ship?
من الذي تظنه يطارد سفينة قبعة القش؟
Oh, yeah!
هكذا إذًا
Answer!
أجيبي
Are you still chasing the Straw Hats' ship, Smoothie?!
هل تتبعين سفينة طاقم قبعة القش يا سموذي؟
Charlotte Smoothie 14th Daughter of the Charlotte Family (One of the Three Sweet Commanders)
الابنة الرابعة عشر لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت سموذي (أحد قادة الحلوى الثلاث)
Yeah, I am, Brother.
أجل، أنا خلفهم يا أخي
You guys keep chasing the Straw Hats' ship!
واصلوا مطاردة سفينة قبعة القش
Bavarois and I are going to chase Bege and Mama!
أما أنا وبافروا، فسنلحق ببيجي وماما
Squeeze every last drop of life out of them!
اعصريهم حتّى آخر قطرة من حياتهم
Torment them and plunge them into an abyss of fear!
عذبيهم وأجعليهم يقاسون معاناة لا مثيل لها
Roger that.
عُلم
He should've just let me handle it from the beginning...
كان يجدر به تكليفي بتولّي أمرهم منذ البداية
Brother Peros is getting distracted...
أخي بيروس مشتت الذهن
Charlotte Citron 15th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة الخامسة عشر لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت سترون
Staying on Cacao Island would've been much easier,
كان يفترض أن نبقى في جزيرة الكاكاو
eating chocolate and drinking tea...
نتناول الشوكولاتة ونحتسي الشاي
They're so impatient. Men are such idiots.
إنّه عديم الصبر حقًّا، يا لغباء الرجال
Charlotte Cinnamon 16th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة السادسة عشر لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت سينامون
Well, don't say that.
حسنًا، حدث ما حدث
Everyone, prepare to fight!
استعدوا للقتال جميعًا
Before they reach Cacao Island, we'll sink the Straw Hats' ship!
سنُغرق سفينة طاقم قبعة القش قبل أن تصل إلى جزيرة الكاكاو
Yeah!
أجل
They know where we're meeting Luffy?!
أيعرفون مكان التقائنا بلوفي؟
Yeah, it's probably surrounded by ships waiting to ambush us.
أجل، على الأرجح أنّ الجزيرة محاطة بأساطيل تنتظرنا
Oh, no...
...محال
Oddly enough, they seem to be acknowledging us as strong opponents.
يبدو أنّهم أصبحوا يعتبروننا تهديدًا حقيقيًّا لهم
Cacao Island will be our final and biggest challenge!
ستكون جزيرة الكاكاو تحدّينا الأكبر والأخير
We'll rescue Luffy no matter what and escape this territory.
سننقذ لوفي مهما كلّف الأمر ونخرج من هذا الإقليم
But... if we fight their fleet head-on, we're bound to lose.
لكننا لن ننجو إن واجهنا أساطيلهم بشكلٍ مباشر
What's with that pitiful look?!
لِمَ تبدو مثيرًا للشفقة؟
I can't believe you slipped...
لا أصدق أنّك انزلقت
Straw Hat!
يا قبعة القش
My plan is going well!
خطتي تسير كما ينبغي
Big Brother!
أخي الكبير
To tell you the truth, I was the one who...
...في ذلك الوقت، أنا من قامت
Oh, I didn't know that, Flambé!
لم أكن أعرف ذلك يا فلامبي
You're such a thoughtful, well-behaved girl!
يا لكِ من فتاة ذكية وماكرة
That's my favorite sister.
كما هو متوقع من أختي المفضلة
Oh, I'm so commendable! And so cute!
يا لي من فتاة يُعتمد عليها وظريفة
That one moment of carelessness...
...مجرد لحظة إهمال
will be the deciding factor in this fight!
بإمكانها قلب موازين المعركة
Why did you lower your guard?!
فلماذا فقدت تركيزك؟
Mochi Anemone!
شقائق نعمان الموتشي
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
ما الخطب يا قبعة القش؟
Just as I began to think highly of you...
...كنتُ للتو قد بدأت باحترامك
you decided to disappoint me!
لكنك خيّبت ظني
I think I saw it!
أظنني رأيتها
Or was it my imagination?
أم أنّها مجرد مخيلتي؟
That's fine.
لا بأس بالمخيلة
Because beyond that imagination is observation haki!
فهاكي الملاحظة امتداد لها
You have to be able to sense it instinctively!
لذا يجب أن تكون قادرًا على الشعور به تلقائيًّا
Instinctively?!
تلقائيًّا؟
He stood up again!
نهض مجدّدًا
What's with those wobbly legs?!
يا له من ترنّح
All right! Another shot, then!
عظيم، رمية أخرى
This time, I'll shoot a numbing needle that's 10 times more effective than the last one!
سأصيبك هذه المرة بإبرة تخدير أكثر تأثيرًا بعشر أضعاف من سابقتها
You're just a monkey who doesn't know when to give up.
أيها القرد الذي لا يعرف معنى الاستسلام
Drop dead already!
فلتهلك حالًا
Numbing Needle!
إبرة التخدير
What? He dodged it! That was my silent needle!
ماذا؟ تفاداها؟ رغم أنّ إبرتي عديمة الصوت
But he fell anyway!
لكنه سقط
Lady Flambé! They'll hear us!
فلامبي-ساما، سيسمعوننا
B-But the way that monkey stands up...
لكن انظر إلى أقدام ذلك القرد إنّها تترنّح وتتخبّط مثل ساقي طفلٍ رضيع
So wobbly!
ترتجف، ترتجف
Come on, don't make us laugh, too!
مهلًا، لا تجعلينا نضحك رجاءً
There, look!
تعالوا انظروا إليه
He's so lame! Even though he's super weak and covered in blood,
يا لسخافته، رغم أنّه ملطخ بالدماء وضعيف إلّا أنّه يواصل النهوض مرارًا وتكرارًا
He wobbles up then gets knocked back down!
ينهض مترنّحًا ويسقط مجدّدًا
And then wobbles his way back up again!
ثم ينهض مترنحًا مرة أخرى
Flambé...?
فلامبي؟
Don't tell me...
...أيعقل أنّها
Big Brother is looking this way!
أخي الكبير ينظر إليّ
He's so perfect and so cool!
إنّه مثالي ورائع فعلًا
What?!
ماذا؟
Well done! You're such a well-behaved girl, Flambé...
عمل جيّد، إنّكِ فتاة ذكية حقًّا يا فلامبي
There, there.
أحسنتِ
He's going to praise me!
سيثني عليّ
I'm not ready for it yet!
لستُ مستعدةً لهذا بعد
I see. It was you, Flambé.
فهمت، أنتِ السبب فيما حدث يا فلامبي
You stopped him with your favorite silent blowgun.
«شللتِ حركته بسلاحك المفضل «إبر التخدير الصامتة
In such an intense battle, his concentration suddenly broke...
مما جعله يفقد تركيزه للحظة أثناء معركتنا المحتدمة
I thought it was strange...
توقعت أنّه ثمة شيء مريب قد حدث
Mochi...
دفعة
Thrust!
الموتشي
But I still attacked him in his moment of weakness, pierced his stomach, and inflicted a fatal wound!
ظللت أهاجمه في لحظة ضعفة وأصبته بجرحٍ قاتل حين طعنت بطنه
Do you think... that I want to win like that?!
أتظنين أنني أريد نصرًا كهذا؟
Look at that, Lady Flambé! The fawn stood up again!
انظري يا فلامبي-ساما الحمل الوديع يحاول النهوض مجدّدًا
Hey, don't make me laugh!
مهلًا، لا تضحكني
His legs are all wobbly!
ساقيه ترتجف
Just like a baby fawn's!
كطفلٍ رضيع
Now, Commander Katakuri will win for sure!
بهذا، سينتصر كاتاكوري-ساما بكل تأكيد
Of course!
بالطبع
It's my perfect big brother's perfect victory!
أخي الكبير المثالي سيظفر بنصر مثالي
Flambé.
فلامبي
Did you do it?
أهذه فعلتك؟
That's right, Big Brother!
هذا صحيح، يا أخي الكبير
I. Did. It.
أنا من قمتُ بذلك
I'm the most considerate and the cutest among your sisters, right?!
من بين جميع أخواتك الصغار أنا الأظرف والأفضل لديك، أليس كذلك؟
The perfect and world's greatest big brother's favorite will be...
الأخت المفضلة لدى أعظم ...أخ كبير في العالم هي
me!
أنا
Pat my head and tell me I'm a good girl!
ربّت على رأسي واسمعني كلمات الثناء والمديح
Big Brother!
أخي الكبير
What do you all find so funny?!
ما المضحك في الأمر؟
He...!
...ذلك
Commander Katakuri!
كاتاكوري-ساما
W-Why?!
لـ-لماذا؟
Don't you dare...
...حين يتقاتل رجلان
give unwanted support in a duel between men!
لا تتدخلي بينهما
Stay away for me! Don't touch me!
ابتعد، لا تلمسني
Commander Katakuri!
كاتاكوري-ساما
If you're going to laugh at that idiot...
...إن كنتم تضحكون على ذلك الأحمق
then you'll have to laugh at me, too!
ينبغي لكم أن تضحكوا عليّ أيضًا
So lame!
يا للسخافة
Agreed! So disappointing!
فعلًا، يا لها من خيبة أمل
Come on, that's gross! You got blood on me!
بئسًا، هذا مقزز، لقد تناثر دمك عليّ
What the hell is this?!
ما الذي تفكر فيه؟
You're supposed to always be noble, calm, strong, and perfect in every way!
لطالما كنت نبيلًا وهادئًا وقويًّا ومثاليًّا في كل شيء
That's the person we admire!
هذا ما أثار إعجابنا بأخانا الكبير
But you stabbed your own stomach...
لكنك طعنت بطنك
So lame! Someone like you can not be Big Brother Katakuri!
يا للسخافة، أنت لست أخي الكبير كاتاكوري
How pathetic!
مثيرٌ للشفقة
You look like a pelican eel!
إنّك تبدو كإنقليس البحر
Pelican eel!
إنقليس البحر
Stop it, Lady Flambé! We won't be able to hold in our laughter!
توقفي يا فلامبي-ساما، لا يمكنني إخفاء ضحكتي
C'mon... How disappointing!
بحق، لقد خيّبت ظني
Whoa, it's a pelican eel!
ها هو إنقليس البحر قادم
Stay away from him!
ابتعدوا عنه
And he's as strong as a monster!
إنّه وحش غريب وقوي
Run!
اهربوا
Hey! Say something!
مهلًا، قل شيئًا
Hurry up and take pictures! Let's show everyone
التقطوا صورًا له، يجب أن نُري الجميع مظهر ذلك الفاشل
E-Excuse me! I'm sorry, Commander Katakuri...
الـ-المعذرة، سامحنا يا كاتاكوري-ساما
Commander Katakuri, look this way!
التفت نحوي من فضلك يا كاتاكوري-ساما
He really looks like a pelican eel.
إنّه يشبه إنقليس البحر حقًّا
The perfect big brother that everyone admired, Charlotte Katakuri,
الأخ الكبير المثالي الذي يحترمه الجميع؛ شارلوت كاتاكوري
is dead!
قد مات
I'll expose you to the fan club and to every island in Totto Land!
سنرسل هذه الصور إلى جميع أعضاء رابطة المعجبين بك في جميع جُزر توتولاند
It will be known throughout the entire country!
سأنشرها في جميع أنحاء الدولة
How dare you get your dirty blood on me...
كيف تجرؤ على تلطيخي بدمائك وتهديد الأخت المفضلة لدى الجميع؟
Now who's the perfect big brother?! You're so uncool!
لم تعد أخي الكبير المثالي، بل مجرد شخص غير رائع
I'm embarrassed to even tell people we're blood-related!
أشعر بالعار من الاعتراف بأنني أختك حتّى
You ruined the tea party and I won't forgive you, either, Straw Hat!
وأنا لن أسامحك على تخريب حفلة الشاي يا قبعة القش
It's so annoying to even lay eyes on you two!
مجرد النظر إليكما يثير غيظي
I'll shoot highly venomous needles through your hearts now!
هذه المرة سأطلق إبرًا سامة لإصابة قلبيكما
Do it! Do it!
افعليها، افعليها
I won't forgive you! Both of you should prepare for what's to come!
لن أغفر لكما، استعدّا لما هو آتٍ
Our spectators sure are noisy...
أولئك المتفرجون مزعجون
They won't be able to stay on their feet anyway!
لن يصمدوا بعد الآن على أي حال
Conqueror's haki?!
الهاكي الملكي؟
That monkey can use it, too?!
ذلك القرد يستخدمه أيضًا؟
A weakling like him...?!
...كيف لضعيف مثله